爽啊 宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
都赏给你吧
Oh, take it all!
不不
Oh, oh, no,
赏给你吧 宝贝
You take it, baby.
不 宝贝 都"给"你吧
No, baby, You take it all!
不 "给"你吧 宝贝
Oh, no, you take it, baby.
不宝贝 都给你啦
No, baby, you take it!
我的神啊
Dear God,
你俩随便一个"收"了行吗
will one of you just take it
赶紧收了了事吧
and get it over with?
麦克斯 我不信听到他俩那声音
Max, there is no way you could be sleeping
你还有办法睡觉
through Oleg and Sophie.
你那样真有效吗
Does that actually work?
有啊
It does,
配上这个就有效
with a little help from this.
给我喝
Give me.
我还以为这酒有点果香呢
I was hoping that'd be fruitier.
他们这边做做
I mean, they're here.
又到那边搞搞
They're there.
然后又到这边爱爱
Then, they're here again.
我们就跟遭空袭的村子一样
It's like we're a village under attack.
没错 要不了多久
Yup, just a matter of time
就会有无人驾驶飞机袭击了
till someone sends in a drone.
而且不光有淫叫声
and it's not just that moaning.
我好像还听到有大球[睾丸]滚动的声音
I think I heard a big ball rolling around up there.
如果有颗睾丸在楼上滚
If a ball is rolling around up there,
奥列格就应该停下送医了
Oleg should stop and see a doctor.
他们还能再更扰邻点吗
This couldn't be any more intrusive.
抱歉抱歉
Sorry about that.
保龄球
A bowling ball?
他们为啥会用到保龄球啊
And why do they need a bowling ball?
可能"洞"不够用了吧
Maybe they ran out of holes.
你们有看到一颗球吗
Have you guys seen a ball?
麦克斯 上菜
Pick up, Max.
抱歉给你们家天花板弄破了个洞
And sorry about the hole in your ceiling.
奥列格 我都懒得叫你
Oleg, I'm not even gonna ask you
管好裤裆里的鸟了
to keep it in your pants anymore,
但你好歹也别让它飞出家门吧
but could you keep it in your apartment?
苏菲
Oh, hey, Sophie.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
春意盎然的季节啊
Oh, spring is in the air.
波兰的这时候
This is the time of year in Poland
积雪会融化
when the snow would melt
那些被冻死的亲戚们
and all our dead relatives
就会顺着雪水流回来
would float back to us.
我没去过欧洲
I've never been to Europe,
但那景色肯定迷人
but it sounds beautiful.
麦克斯 卡洛琳呢
Max, where is Caroline?
别跟我说她在女厕里
And don't tell me she's in the ladies' room,
我已经从下面偷看了每个隔间了
because I already peeked under all those stalls.
她不在里面
She wasn't there.
但我看到了些"东西"
But I saw things.
恭喜你终于看到那些"东西"了
Well, congratulations on finally seeing those things.
她迟到二十分钟了
She's 20 minutes late,
作为一个老板 我无法接受
and, as the boss, I will not have it.
某人早上婴儿床起错边 脾气暴躁啊
Wow, someone woke up on the wrong side of his crib.
你迟到了 太超过了
You're late. This is unacceptable.
别理他
Don't mind him.
他刚第一次见到女人的下面
He just saw his first vagina,
他气炸了
and he's furious.
是这样的
Okay, here's the thing.
我不得不多睡一下
I had to take a nap
因为奥列格与苏菲昨晚"激战"了一整夜
because Oleg and Sophie were having sex all night long.
才没有呢
Not true.
我们有休息一下 看个黄片
We took a break to watch a porno.
守时
Punctuality
是我写在员工手册
is the number one rule in my employee handbook,
又名"阿憨手册"[音似]的第一准则
which I've adorably named The Han-book.
别紧张 阿憨
Relax, Han.
我没来给客人
Nobody's gonna die
端金枪鱼三明治 客人也不会死啦
if I'm not here to drop off a tuna melt.
其实 我真给他们上菜
In fact, they're more likely to die
他们吃了还更可能会死呢
if I do drop it off.
迟到了还这么嚣张
Late, and with an attitude.
你觉得在这干活很掉价吗
You think you're too good for the diner?
她当然是这么想啦
Of course she thinks that.
这店连酸酵种面包都不配卖好吗
I think sourdough bread is too good for this diner.
那你又有什么其他工作选择呢 卡洛琳
Well, what other career option do you have, Caroline?
比如说 小蛋糕店吗
Hmm, let's see. Cupcakes?
不 你那店开张不到半年就倒了
No, wait, your shop didn't last six months.
别哪壶不开提哪壶
Don't go there, Han.
我偏要提 我提起又放下了
Oh, I'm already there. And now I'm back.
干嘛这么大脾气啊 阿憨
Why so moody, Han?
你"大姨夫"来了吗
Are you man-struating?
又到了每月[男人]流血的时候了吗
Is it that time of the man-th?
阿憨 那店是我们的梦想
That shop was our dream, Han,
而你这只是个傻逼餐厅
and this is just a dumb diner.
你被炒了
You're fired.
还炒我啊
Ooh! I'm fired?
麦克斯 阿憨炒了我呢
Max, Han just fired me.
你个幸运的小骚货
You lucky son of a whore.
卡洛琳 我是认真的
I'm serious, Caroline.
你居然说我的餐厅"傻逼"
You called my diner "dumb."
好歹我的餐厅现在还没倒闭 开得好好的
Well, at least my diner's still open and successful,
但你的傻逼小蛋糕店 都傻逼得倒闭了吧
whereas your cupcake shop was so dumb, it failed.
他不是真提了这壶吧
Ooh, he did not go there.
我就提这壶 然后又放下
I went there, and then I came back,
然后我再提一遍
and then I went there again.
我干嘛要受你的气
You know what? I don't need this.
因为我们还真需要这薪水
Well, actually, you do kinda need this
我俩是穷光蛋
'cause we broke.
管它的
Broke or not,
老娘就是不要在这听他放屁
I don't have to stand here and take this.
我不干了
I quit.
是吗 你不干啦
Oh, really? You quit?
你脑子比我这餐厅还傻逼吧
You must be dumber than my diner
你都被炒了 还怎么不干
because I already fired you.
阿憨 我知道你火气上脑到这高度了
Han, I know you've had it up to here,
但你太过了
but you need to relax.
你能相信阿憨居然炒了我吗
Can you believe Han fired me?
他想啥 凭啥呢[停下]
I mean, where does he get off?
大概会在《吸血鬼猎人巴菲》聊天室驻足吧
Probably in Buffy the Vampire Slayer chat rooms.
你不会是一直站在门口等我回家吧
Have you been standing here by the door this whole time?
我连去尿尿都不敢
I didn't even pee.
就怕错过你进门
I was afraid I'd miss you.
所以先等我一下吧
So, hold on.
所以你今天过得跟小狗一样嘛
So, basically, You had the same day as a puppy?
我在那工作是他的福气
Han's lucky I work there.
我让他的餐厅变得高级和有档次
I bring class and sophistication to that place.
没厕纸了
There's no toilet paper,
最后一张咖啡滤纸我也用掉啦
and I just used the last coffee filter.
你还真是让那间厕所
You are sophisticatin' the hell
变得无比高级呀
out of that toilet right now.
而且啊
And you know what?
你可以告诉阿憨
You can tell Han that the only way
要我回去的唯一办法就是他来道歉
I am ever going back there is if he apologizes.
可以 但首先呢
Okay, but first,
他也留话要我对你说
he wanted me to tell you this.
你唯一能回去的方式呢
The only way you're ever going back there
就是你跟他道歉
is if you apologize.
要我道歉 他想都别想
Well, an apology from me is not happening.
爽啊 宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
都赏给你吧
Ooh, take it all.
不
Oh, oh, no,
都给你吧 亲爱的
you take it, baby.
宝贝
Oh, baby--
这今晚也不许再发生了
And that is not happening again tonight either.
又来啊
Again?
那可能砸到我们呢
That could've hit us.
这才叫"危险性行为"啊
Now, that's unsafe sex.
我们还送他们的性爱保龄球回来
I think it's pretty neighborly of us
还真是够敦亲睦邻的啊
to return someone's sex bowling ball.
这双手套之后得去埋了才行
You know we have to bury those mitts now.
无论他们在玩什么花样
And we have to tell them to stop
我们都得叫他们停下
whatever it is they're doing up here.
估计是7 10号瓶分叉球吧
Probably a 7-10 split.
现在他们又消停了
And now they're not making noise.
感觉就像去动物园时
It's like when you go to the zoo,
狮子跑进山洞内休息了
and the lion goes inside.
是麦克斯跟卡洛琳
It's Max and Caroline.
你们的球又掉进我们家了
Your ball came into our yard again.
现在有点不太方便
Hi. Yeah, it's not a good time.
我们在玩角色扮演
Uh, we're role-playing,
我在扮碧昂丝
and, obviously, I'm Beyonce.
杰斯
Hey, Jay Z?
看看这些单身女郎们啊[碧昂丝歌曲]
Look at all the single ladies.
好啊 宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
杰斯跟我有很多共同之处
Jay Z and I have a lot in common.
他买下职篮布鲁克林篮网队
He bought the Brooklyn Nets.
我则是在布鲁克林买的发网
I bought my hairnets in Brooklyn.
你们扮杰斯与碧昂丝我一点都不意外
I'm not surprised that you're Jay Z and Beyonce,
不过他们打保龄球我倒很惊讶
but I am kinda surprised that they bowl.
这要我放哪
Where should I put this?
我告诉你们我对他说的吧
Oh, well, I'll tell you what I told him.
你想把它放哪都行
Put it anywhere You want.
所以现在这颗球基本算我们的了
So that's basically our ball at this point.
我知道你们俩爱得疯狂
Look, you two may be crazy in love,
但我们也要被你们搞疯了
but your love is driving us crazy.
爱得疯狂吗
Crazy in love?
拜托 我们才不相爱
Oh, come on. We're not in love.
我们只是炮友而已
Oleg and I are just shtup buddies.
炮友吗
Shtup buddies?
我们不止如此吧
I wouldn't say that's all we are.
我错了 你说的有道理
Oh, no, you're right.
我们还共用一张药房集奖卡
We also share a CVS points reward card.
如果是药房给的东西 能算是奖励吗
Is it really a reward if it comes from CVS?
你们难道就不能去奥列格家"做"吗
Can't you two ever do it over at Oleg's apartment?
还是他睡的路边都停满车了
Or are all the lanes reserved?
我完全不知道他住哪里
I have no idea where he lives.
等等 你还没去过奥列格家吗
Wait, you've never been to Oleg's apartment?
没有 我工作这么忙
No, with my busy work schedule,
我哪有空去注射
I don't have the time to get
去他家需要打的疫苗啊
the battery of shots that I would need.
看到我家会吓死你的 苏菲
You'd be surprised by my apartment, Sophie.
那里可不光只是
It's more than just the place
四重高潮的发源地呢
the quadruple orgasm was born.
这听起来倒是很棒啊
Yeah, well, That sounds nice.
碧昂...
Oh, yes. Beyonc--
碧昂丝的头发掉了
Um, Beyonce's hair just fell out.
我先去拿我的热熔胶枪黏上
I gotta go get my hot glue gun.
女孩们 我有点夸大我家了
Girls, I may have oversold my apartment.
跟她说不需要先打疫苗吗
What, by saying she won't need to get shots?
是是是
Yes.
你们俩个可以来帮忙布置一下吧
Maybe you two could help me fix it up a little,
添加点女人元素
give it a feminine touch.
我不干
Well, I'm out.
我愿意帮你
You know what? I'll do it.
但我最近刚失业
But I'm very recently out of work,
所以帮忙的部分是要收费的
so I'm gonna have to charge you.
如果你不收钱 那你就会是
If you didn't, you'd be the only girl
第一个进他家又不收他钱的女人了
who ever went to his apartment without getting paid.
成交
You got a deal.
奥列格家肯定是这间
Oleg's apartment's this way.
我闻到了体香剂的味道了
I can smell the AXE body spray.
我们把这几个枕头布置进去
I'll just throw a couple of these pillows around,
然后就可以走了
and then we'll be gone.
我真不敢相信我要自己步入他家里
I can't believe I'm walking up to Oleg's apartment.
我一直以为那天会是我被他下药迷晕
I always thought I'd be dragged here unconscious
嘴被胶带封住 然后拖进去的
with electrical tape over my mouth.
女孩们 下午好
Afternoon, ladies.
这里就是奇迹[魔术]发生之地了
This is where the magic happens.
我肯定你肯定让不少女人在里面"消失"过
Well, I'm sure you've made some women disappear here.
好吧
Okay.
就我第一眼的观察判断
Just off the top of my head,
起码就还需要不少可爱枕头了
I think we're gonna need a couple more pillows.
如果把公寓弄成这样
If you keep your apartment Like this,
是不是就能按1980年的物价付租金啊
do you get to pay 1980s rent prices?
你们都还没看到最棒的地方呢
You haven't even seen the best part yet.
瞧
Look.
我要走上天堂的阶梯了
Goin' up the stairway to heaven, baby.
没错 就是这里啦
Oh, yeah. There it is.
这就是我的床
That's my bed.
这是哪啊 69夜店吗
Where are we? Studio 69?
那可是1500颗灯泡组成
That's 1,500 tracer bulbs.
都是我从皇后区的电影院拆来的
I tore most of them out of the new Cineplex 14 in Queens.
首先 我闻到了一股
First of all, I am smelling something
只能解释为反除汗味剂的味道
that can only be described as anti-antiperspirant.
第二
And, secondly...
不会有女人想走进这里的
no woman wants to walk into this.
根据这个显示
According to this,
685个女人进来过了
685 already have.
其实是1685个
Actually, it's 1,685.
过一千后 那个计数器就归零了
After a thousand, the counter resets.
如果你不想苏菲觉得
look, if you don't want Sophie to feel
自己在排队等着进机动车辆管理局
like she's next in line at the DMV...
其实是性病传染局吧
More like the S-T-D-mv.
-那我们有很多地方需要改进 -好吧
- Then we have a lot of work to do. - Okay.
弄得浪漫一点
Make it look romantic.
当她走进的那一刻 要她觉得自己很特别
When she comes in, I want her to feel special,
感觉自己是第一个走进这里的女人
like she's the only woman that's ever been here
今天第一个
today.
咱们坐下来好好谈吧
Let's just sit down and talk about this.
天啊 麦克斯 她死了吗
Oh, my God. Max, is she dead?
不是啦 她是阿丽西斯
No. She's Alexis.
你居然有个人体仿真性爱玩偶
You have one of those anatomically-correct real dolls!
很少看到她旁边没有个
It's rare to see one without a short, fat man
矮肥短鸡鸡的男人呢
standing next to it with a button penis.
这原价要6000块
They sell for $6,000,
但我半价买到了
but I got her for half off.
她是"已被人疼爱过"的
She was previously loved.
麦克斯 你不许那样
Max, you are not doing that.
去你的不许
The hell I'm not.
这是我唯一一次看完裸女后
This is my one chance to see a woman naked
不用再跟她们抱抱的机会
without having to spoon her after.
佩服佩服
Respect.
你这里有很多"个人风格"鲜明的东西
Well, you've made a lot of strong choices here,
但我不确定它们放在一起搭不搭
but I'm not sure they're all working together.
比如说 那个性爱秋千就跟山羊对冲
For example, that sex swing is fighting the goat.
等你去给我们弄来橡胶手套后
Now, why don't we start by you going
我们就动手开始改造吧
and getting us some rubber gloves?
手套记得多弄点
Lots of them,
以及市面上最强的漂白剂以及肥皂
and the strongest bleach and soap products you can find.
还有一套生化防护服
Oh, and a hazmat suit.
别担心尺寸大小 我可以系腰带
Don't worry about the size. I can belt it.
但我的好东西你会留着的 对吧
But you're gonna keep my good stuff, right?
如果我看见有的话 会考虑保留
If I see any, I'll consider it.
快去
Go.
那你打算怎么处置阿丽西斯
What are you going to do with Alexis?
先送康复中心 再送到蒙大拿州妇女收容所
Rehab, and then a women's shelter in Montana.
快去
Go!
我有很多工作要做
I've got a lot of work to do.
但首先
But first...
忍不住啊
Can not do it.
实在忍不住
你能把那个关掉吗 麦克斯
Can you please turn that off, Max?
我都开始觉得头晕了
I'm starting to feel a little dizzy...
我可不能晕倒在这地上
And I can't fall on the floor,
可能会被不明液体黏住
'cause I might stick to it.
你没必要干这种工作
You don't have to do this!
快打电话给阿憨道歉
Just call Han and apologize,
然后在梅毒攻击前
and we can get outta here
咱们赶紧闪人
before the syphilis sets in.
不要 他对我说了一些很伤人的话
No, he said some really hurtful things to me,
我宁愿待在这里
and I'd rather stay here
为奥列格和阿丽西斯工作
and work for Oleg and Alexis.
至少我的尊严还在
At least I'll have my dignity.
容许我先失陪了
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我得爬上精床探险号[星际迷航]
I have to go climb the sperm-ship enterprise.
先把窗帘拉开
Let me just get these curtains open
好让我能看清楚这里
so I can see better.
看清楚点
Seeing better?
这不太对吧
Is that the way to go?
我走在一张水床上
I'm walking on a water bed.
这比想象中的要难[硬]啊
This is harder than it looks.
这句话不知道在这张床上说过多少遍了
How many times has that been said on this bed?
我的鞋跟
Oh, my heel!
我咽下去了
I swallowed!
我不小心咽下去了
I accidentally swallowed.
这句话肯定也常有人说
You know that's been said.
麦克斯 有个问题
Max, we got a problem.
看见那个女孩了吗
See that girl?
干嘛 像平时那样吗
Oh, what? The usual drill?
你抓住她的手臂
You hold her arms,
我揍到她愿意给百分之二十的小费吗
and I punch her till she tips 20%?
虽然我很喜欢这么做
As much as I enjoy that when we do it,
但不是
no.
她是来应征卡洛琳的工作
She's here to apply for Caroline's job.
什么
What?
阿憨是来真的吗
Han's really going through with this?
我以为他只是说说而已
I thought It was all talk,
就像吉娃娃冲着大狗叫 也只是叫叫而已
like when a chihuahua barks at a big dog.
我也是 我以为会这事很快会消失
Me too. I thought it would blow over.
就像阿憨上次被风吹不见那样
You know, like Han did in the wind that time?
但这次不是 他是来真的
But, no, He is serious.
不行 我来解决
No way. I got this.
你好 这是你的简历吗
Hi, is that your resume?
让我看看
Let's take a little look-see.
你还在那工作过啊 真厉害
Oh, you worked there? Cool.
是的 我工作非常努力
Yep. I'm a very hard worker.
很好 你会挡拳头吗
Good. Can you block a punch?
因为老板会打人哦
'Cause the owner hits us.
他把我大腿打骨折了 当我抱怨时
He broke my femur. When I complained,
他又打折了我另一条腿
he broke the other one.
在他看见咱俩说话前 快跑
Run before he sees me talking to you.
厄尔 我得让阿憨和卡洛琳和好
Earl, I gotta get Han aAnd Caroline to make up.
我得靠吃药才愿留下工作
I don't have access to the pills I need
她不在我就买不起了
to keep working here without her.
你有什么建议或药吗
Any advice or pills?
我想想 我们在这里像是一家人
Well, let's see. We are kind of like a family here,
除了我周末见你不用有人监视
except I can see you unsupervised on the weekends.
而你也没拿我上大学的钱
And you didn't use my college fund
给已婚男人买跑车
to buy a married man a Corvette.
在我的家庭
And in my family,
当我的孩子吵架时
when my kids would fight,
我会试图让他们跟对方说话
I tried to get them to talk to each other,
因为坦诚是关键
because honesty is key.
但如果不管用
But if that didn't work,
我会骗他们
I'd lie to their faces--
把他们关进房间 然后告诉他们
lock them in their room and tell them
对方只剩三周可以活了
that the other one had three weeks to live.
这在以前 就可以算是模范家长呢
You know, what used to be known as good parenting.
麦克斯 我有12个资历过硬的候选人
Max, I've got 12 overqualified candidates
今天来应征服务员的工作
coming in for the waitress position today.
真要多谢现在不景气的经济
Thank you, crumbling economy!
阿憨 在这家餐厅
You know, Han, here at this diner,
我们就像是一家人
we're kind of like a little family, and--
我编不下去了
Oh, I can't do this.
卡洛琳就剩三周可以活了
Caroline has three weeks left to live.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
她喝了奥列格水床的水
She drank Oleg's water bed.
迟早会挂掉的
It's just a matter of time.
想得美 麦克斯
Nice try, Max.
我不会把工作还给她的
I'm not going to give her back her job.
她在跟我装逼之前
She should've checked herself
应该先掂掂自己斤两的
before she wrecked herself.
拜托啦 把她请回来
Come on. Hire her back.
当个大气的男人
Be the bigger man.
声明一下
And note,
我不是在拿你的身材开玩笑
I did not make a short joke,
因为这事真的很重要
because this is important,
同时也因为我还在想怎么用
and also because I'm still working on something
彼特·丁拉基的名字开玩笑
with Peter Dinklage's name.
不行 麦克斯 我的立场很坚定
No way, Max. I am holding firm.
硬气的阿憨蛮性感的
You know, firm Han is kinda hot.
-是吗 -是的
- He is? - Yeah.
我有点喜欢硬气的阿憨
I'm kinda feeling firm Han.
虽然我对其他会硬的部位没兴趣
I have no interest in feeling the firm part,
但我可以考虑跟你约会
but I'll hang out with the rest.
你居然想跟我约会
You want to hang out with me?
我基本周一到周五都有空
I'm generally free Mondays through Fridays,
白天和晚上都行
mornings and evenings,
而且我周末也空得很
and my weekends are wide open.
虽然我6月可能要参加婚礼 但...
I may have a wedding to go to in June, but--
深呼吸
Breathe.
明天来我家
Come over tomorrow.
卡洛琳会去奥列格家
Caroline Will be at Oleg's.
我们可以嗑药磕到嗨 然后看电影
We can get stoned and watch a movie.
我上一次还是在演唱会上
The last time I was stoned
因误吸别人抽大麻吐出来的烟而嗨翻天
was from a contact high I got at a concert.
演唱会的人们很容易变得疯狂啊
Well, those wiggle shows do get crazy.
瞧瞧咱俩 麦克斯
Look at us, Max,
就像好朋友那样
hanging outside of work at your place
下班后照样出来厮混
like a couple of homeys.
是啊 我的好朋友在哪里
Yeah, and where is my homey?
这边
Oh, it's this way.
我闻到了体香剂的味道
I can smell the AXE body spray.
我们该看什么电影呢
Now, what movie should we watch?
我带了《怪物史瑞克》第一部 第二部
I brought Shrek, Shrek 2,
第三部 还有3D版的
Shrek 3, Shrek 3-d,
以及卡梅隆·迪亚兹照顾癌症病患的电影
and that Cameron Diaz cancer movie.
是史瑞克得了癌症那部吗
Is there one where Shrek has cancer?
这里完全
This is completely--
就是我一直住的地方
the same place I always live at.
麦克斯 这里真漂亮
Max, it's so pretty.
我还以为你家会有
I thought your place would have furniture
用刮胡刀片做的家具呢
made out of razor blades or something.
我还想呢 那听起来超屌
I wish. That sounds bitchin'.
你们俩在这里干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
卡洛琳在这里干嘛
What is Caroline doing here?
你不是说她会在奥列格家吗
You said she was going to be at Oleg's.
我就是在奥列格家啊
I am at Oleg's.
你们俩跟奥列格一起住吗
You guys live with Oleg?
你告诉他这里是我们的公寓吗
You told him this was our apartment?
一位智者告诉我
As a wise person once told me,
有时为了家庭和睦 可以撒撒小谎
sometimes, you gotta lie to keep your family together.
在你们跟对方说话前
I'm not letting anyone leave
谁也别想走
until you talk to each other.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们不是要抽大麻吗
Are we not smoking weed?
我已经抽了
Oh, I already did.
我不知道他哪有毛病
I don't know what his problem is.
我错过20分钟上班时间就炒了我
He fired me for missing 20 minutes of work.
他何不因为错过青春期而炒了他自己呢
Why doesn't he fire himself for missing puberty?
任她说吧 阿憨
Let it go, Han.
她整个早上都在擦捆绑式假阳具上的灰尘
She spent her morning dusting a strap-on.
我不是因为你迟到而炒了你
I didn't fire you because you were late.
我炒你是因为你说餐厅的坏话
I fired you because you crapped all over the diner,
你忘了在你一无所有的时候
and you forgot that diner lifted you up
是餐厅把你救起来
when you had nothing.
在你拿不到玉米罐时
Well, I lifted you up
还是我把你举"起来"的呢
when you couldn't reach the canned corn.
所以我们扯平了 争吵结束
So, we're even. Fight over.
你把我公寓搞成什么鬼样子了
What the hell did you do to my apartment?
看起来就像拍
It looks like you could film
阴道清洗液的广告现场
a douche commercial in here.
奥列格 这就是你想要的效果
Oleg, this is what you asked for:
-浪漫 -浪漫吗
- Romantic. - Romantic?
我家从淫乱天堂变成了
My place went from Fifty Shades Of Grey
屎黄色地狱
to fifty shades of beige.
我的性爱秋千呢
Where's my sex swing?
我的性爱椅子呢
Where's my sex chair?
我的那张上面写着
Where's my poster that says,
"捅她前面 舔她后面"的海报呢
"Poke her in the front, lick her in the back"?
奥列格 冷静
Oleg, relax.
你东西不是在地下室就在衣柜
All your stuff's either in the basement or the closet.
我觉得我更了解
And I think would know more about what a woman
女人喜欢的家的样子
would like to come home to
这至少比一个男人的前女友
than a man whose last girlfriend
是用菲律宾橡胶做的强
was made in the Philippines.
我来了
It's me!
赶紧把孩子藏起来
Hide your kids!
把你老婆也藏起来
Hide your wife!
苏菲
Sophie!
她不能知道你们在这里
She can't know you're here.
快走 你们快走
Go, go, all of you.
阿憨 躲进衣柜里
Han! Get in the closet!
叫一个还没出柜的男人躲进衣柜
Putting a guy who's in the closet in the closet?
就像基佬版嵌套娃娃一样
That's like gay nesting dolls.
我不是基佬
I'm not gay.
我是都市花美男
I'm a metrosexual.
这里就是奇迹发生之地吗
This is where the magic happens?
不是吧
Oh, no.
你是跟你妈一起住吗
Do you live With your mother?
怎么 你不喜欢吗
What? You don't like?
你以为你会喜欢一些女性的元素
I thought you would enjoy the girl's touch.
什么女性
What girls?
黄金女郎吗
The Golden Girls?
苏菲不喜欢
Sophie hates it.
我应该直接把一只煮熟的火腿扔床上的
I should've just thrown a boiled ham on the bed.
不要啊
Oh, no.
我的头发被奥列格的衣服夹住了
My hair's stuck in Oleg's clothes.
拜托千万不要被裤子拉链夹到
Please don't let it be a pant zipper.
阿憨 这位是阿丽西斯
Han, Alexis.
阿丽西斯 这位是阿憨
Alexis, Han.
快把她从我身上拿开
Ew, take it away from me.
还真沉 不要 不要啊
It's so heavy-- oh, no, oh, no.
救命啊 快把她弄开
Help. Get her off of me.
为什么 你终于有机会"爽一下"了
Why? You're finally getting some.
拿开 拿开
Take it, take it.
我在弄 我在弄
I got it, I got it.
瞧 阿憨摔倒[堕落]了
Look! Han's fallen
而且他"起"不来了
and he can't get it up!
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
重口如我也觉得这场面太恶心
I mean, this is freaky even for me.
苏菲 我可以解释
Sophie, I can explain.
我请卡洛琳来帮我重新布置公寓
I hired Caroline to redo my apartment
好让它看起来不像你预期中的
so it wouldn't be the dirty bachelor pad
那种下流单身汉公寓
you were expecting.
但你就是我预期中的那种下流单身汉
But you are the dirty Bachelor that I'm expecting.
为什么你要请卡洛琳啊
And why would you hire Caroline?
她根本不懂什么是性感
She doesn't know about sexy stuff.
她甚至连我们拿那个保龄球
She couldn't even figure out what we do
来做什么都不知道
with the bowling ball.
苏菲 你真该看看这公寓之前的模样
Sophie, you should've seen what was in here.
他有一个符合人体仿真的性爱娃娃
I mean, he had this anatomically correct real doll
还帮她取名叫阿丽西斯
He named Alexis.
是吗 她可真漂亮
Yeah, well, she's very pretty.
他有一个性爱秋千
He had a sex swing.
哇 性爱秋千
Ooh, a sex swing.
你接下来还要说什么
What are you gonna tell me now?
说他有一张水床吗
That he had a water bed?
我的确曾有
I did.
上面有一千五百个灯泡
It had 1,500 tracer bulbs.
非常香艳
It was hot.
那床现在在谁手里
Well, who has it now?
我要跟他在一起
I wanna be with him.
靠 我已经厌倦那些角色扮演了
Oh, hell, I'm tired of all this role-playing,
所以我要直说
so I'm just going to say it.
苏菲 我爱上你了
Sophie, I am in love with you.
我很久很久
Well, I haven't said this to a man
没对男人这么说了
in a very long time,
但我有一点点喜欢你
but I like you a little bit.
我不懂她为什么这么说 卡洛琳
I don't know what she's talking about, Caroline.
我觉得很漂亮
I think it's pretty.
你让一切都变得更漂亮
You make everything prettier,
连我那家傻逼餐厅也是
even the dumb diner.
你的餐厅才不傻逼
Your diner's not dumb.
我好想它
I miss the diner.
它也很想你
And it misses you.
你可以回来工作
You can have your job back.
是因为我现在嗨翻天
Is it just 'cause I'm stoned,
还是有人也感受到了他们之间的深情
or did anyone else feel that deep connection between them?
你们能离开这里吗
Could you all leave?
我想单独跟奥列格
I wanna be alone with Oleg...
还有阿丽西斯玩会儿
And Alexis.
我们现在要去抽大麻了吗
Now are we going to smoke weed?
是的 我超级想看你嗨的样子
Yeah, I'm dying to see you high.
看你到底能有多嗨[高]
Well, as high as you can get.